{
  "events": {
    "GMI": {
      "artistSummit#1": {
        "polygon": {
          "front": "0x3bC871313BD161aA9834f5A43d625c87cB381244",
          "back": "0x203DbF25DB4d0857654d41436F68897aD8560Daf",
          "left": "0xa4c9a6Fdf153775229a7aBe5756E1e8519C0c912",
          "right": "0xbA842863635D1c0979d1DE451ED5eB40241233CC"
        },
        "mumbai": {
          "front": "0xC83b1f5b2145406DaF7AAFFE53ad1Cb8e82bAEB7",
          "back": "0xEDbd2Fa151Fe3248dFc21CF1F7E181b460a53D8B",
          "left": "0xD9BADcA32Bc58c1D83673D2492028a1BA0df19a9",
          "right": "0x340A84D4b8EE96b22Ac49379C11dB4a68C9BA046"
        }
      }
    }
  },
  "common": {
    "leftSide": { "mumbai": "0x629140D237Afd97ee733cD9638869354F0412331"},
    "rightSide": { "mumbai": "0x3d5e5Af886C947CDC1637BaDaD40F80Bf8973906"},
    "level0": {
      "mumbai": {
        "front": "0x6A4b31558c3A103EDEF74fE773Fd5935964f71EC",
        "back": "0x909CD284182167E21C09162f482F814e1Ca9Ad9f"
      }
    },
    "level1": {
      "mumbai": {
        "front": "0xF0214EDfBE43ff8E2420558E91D14887Cbf80F98",
        "back": "0x26a077EafD1ce79d7B8630D2B43C82E1Ccc4602f"
      }
    },
    "level2": {
      "mumbai": {
        "front": "0x4f1bBfeA50b3BFbDa710642643AFB870772b45BD",
        "back": "0xC06BCB03567EF4096F78b249974C8e9BF723C728"
      }
    },
    "level3": {
      "mumbai": {
        "front": "0x1C4C3Bb8c5DdfD2016695D60d8f60e78B056D7fb",
        "back": "0xB2AE61d076aF50C902D4Dc88A6C866BfBc92a5c3"
      }
    },
    "level4": {
      "mumbai": {
        "front": "0xdbACfd4375c06345cFf4d0153cA20f64B3B6D026",
        "back": "0xfeD9276eB8E680A6c3D9549499c9330dB2d48D91"
      }
    },
    "level5": {
      "mumbai": {
        "front": "0x0C67Ec35C59e70416cFAc2cAe1Afe5d1E1AE5126",
        "back": "0x273032a0b85A2e94685C6c215C498FAC41FB3751"
      }
    },
    "level6": {
      "mumbai": {
        "front": "0x8eCD23330989e1F9AE3b2554bDac9111dAa7bb1B",
        "back": "0x5DF1DF806952505254E22b8724BE13e841ca2Ed4"
      }
    },
    "level7": {
      "mumbai": {
        "front": "0x3AdE914e5Ae6D04E9de67235eFCDE5688164f7d4",
        "back": "0xae1f5Cf31f334Ae5D556a25CBAE70944bd4C9103"
      }
    },
    "level8": {
      "mumbai": {
        "front": "0x90692d7aEAe84aA71dE1f0566c9D0aac662D5021",
        "back": "0xF1dBf93a9DEe5DB638feB5B9c0B6247823d5D704"
      }
    },
    "level9": {
      "mumbai": {
        "front": "0x80edb6b1133D19e7f1b11c618E886b97488ab80E",
        "back": "0x3b4Bd66a6FBFF4E2A866e2284D3974CDDCCb1c08"
      }
    },
    "level10": {
      "mumbai": {
        "front": "0x27478f9BCE3a07ca70C5E6Ead917394464129B6F",
        "back": "0xaF3234254F4e83D03ba9F8d42c49084d3cC46B2f"
      }
    },
    "level11": { "mumbai": "0x26E09d50c84a0185c47Fc36d9b958831Bc4Db557" },
    "level12": { "mumbai": "0x63A74ed478Ae8dBCb660E61BB66cf4EAcfABe090" },
    "level13": { "mumbai": "0x5A46d849091B5AD232ab3bfc8B49E2D83605EAFB" }
  },
  "secret": {
    "secretLevel2": { "mumbai": "0xbDed86cf2F797fc0FFe08113B557B87B9fd6996f" },
    "secretLevel5": { "mumbai": "0x03AE82527c64d670110140fec03CC53B89f865AD" },
    "secretLevel12": { "mumbai": "0x52CB8Fe649964a4c81ECb36C135268aD3352bcaF" }
  },
  "hacker": {
    "hackerLevel5": { "mumbai": "0xB84B23B87cCb3687FE7Da7a2EBd37eeFc88E30f8" }
  }
}
